Guide to the History of Education Society collection, 1960-2013 MS2341
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Journal - History of Education Quarterly, 1961-2011; Series 3
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 14 number 1, 1974; Series (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 14 number 2, 1974; Series (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 14 number 3, 1974; Series (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 14 number 4, 1974; Series (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 15 number 1, 1975; Series (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 15 number 2, 1975; Series (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 15 number 3, 1975; Series (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 15 number 4, 1975; Series (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 16 number 1, 1976; Series (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 16 number 2, 1976; Series (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 16 number 3, 1976; Series (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 16 number 4, 1976; Series (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 17 number 1, 1977; Series (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 17 number 2, 1977; Series (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 17 number 3, 1977; Series (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 17 number 4, 1977; Series (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 18 number 1, 1978; Series (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 18 number 2, 1978; Series (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 18 number 3, 1978; Series (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 18 number 4, 1978; Series (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 19 number 1, 1979; Series (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 19 number 2, 1979; Series (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 19 number 3, 1979; Series (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 19 number 4, 1979; Series (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - History of Education Quarterly volume 20 number 1, 1980; Series (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - History of Education Quarterly volume 20 number 2, 1980; Series (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - History of Education Quarterly volume 20 number 4, 1980; Series (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - History of Education Quarterly volume 20 number 3, 1980; Series (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - History of Education Quarterly volume 21 number 1, 1981; Series (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - History of Education Quarterly volume 21 number 2, 1981; Series (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - History of Education Quarterly volume 21 number 3, 1981; Series (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - History of Education Quarterly volume 21 number 4, 1981; Series (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 22 number 1, 1982; Series (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 22 number 2, 1982; Series (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 22 number 3, 1982; Series (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 22 number 4, 1982; Series (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 23 number 1, 1983; Series (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 22 number 2, 1983; Series (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 22 number 3, 1983; Series (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 22 number 4, 1983; Series (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - History of Education Quarterly volume 24 number 1, 1984; Series (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - History of Education Quarterly volume 24 number 2, 1984; Series (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - History of Education Quarterly volume 24 number 3, 1984; Series (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - History of Education Quarterly volume 24 number 4, 1984; Series (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - History of education archives, 1982; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - History of education quarterly, Undated; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 25, 1985; Series 3 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 26, 1986; Series 3 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 27, 1987; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 29 [1/2], 1989; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 29 [2/2], 1989; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 30 [1/2], 1990; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 30 [2/2], 1990; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 31, 1991; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 32, 1992; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 33, 1993; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 34, 1994; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 35, 1995; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 36, 1996; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 37, 1997; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 38, 1998; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 39, 1999; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 40, 2000; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 44, 2004; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - History of Education Quarterly, vol. 45, 2005; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 46 No. 2, 2006; Series 3 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - History of Education Society Volume 50 Nos. 1 & 2, 2010; Series 3 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - History of Education Quarterly Volume 52 No. 3, 2012; Series 3 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Ideology and Evaluation: In Quest of Meritocracy, 1973; Series 3 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - A Revisionists Response to Maxine Greene's "Identities and Contours: An Approach to Educational History", Undated; Series 3 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - "Schooling and Social Mobility in the Nineteenth-Century South: Georgia, 1840-1890" A Research Proposal, Undated; Series 3 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square and University College of Arts and Science Faculty Commission on the Undergraduate Curriculum, Undated; Series 3 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Religious education, Dates not yet determined; Series 4
- History of Education Quarterly restricted content, 1982-2011; MS2341 Series 5; 6 Linear Feet approximately 12 document boxes
  Conditions Governing Access
  Within the records of the initial donation March 2015 the "accepted and rejected manuscripts" submitted to the History of Education Quarterly are restricted from use for 50 years from date of donation. This is to protect the privacy of authors and peer reviewers. Future donations that have content governed by the addendum to the deed of gift will not be added to the collection management system prior to the end of the restriction and therefore not be described in this series.
  This series contains accepted and rejected manuscript submissions that contain personally identifiable information.
  This series contains one subseries. This arrangement allows GW to make public that this series exists while suppressing the records that within the folder titles may contain restricted information. This arrangement will allow GW to close there records, but retain the descriptive metadata and make it easier to open to users when the restriction ends.